A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Offices xFA116
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Field Offices - Mexico, 1943-1965; 13; 30 Cubic Feet 72 document cases
  - General Office Files, 1943-1965; 1
    - Corn Breeding (OEE) - Reports, 1948-1959 (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - Corn Collection Program/Mexico and Central America - 1952-1955 Corn Diseases - 1959 Corn Germ Plasm - 1956-1959, 1952-1959 (Box 11, Folder 137)
    - Corn Improvement Program - Conferences, 1954, 1956, 1958, 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - Corn Improvement Program - Proposal (Marte R. Gomez), 1944 (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - Corn Improvement Program - Reports, 1943-1959 (Box 11, Folder 140)
    - Corn Papers - E.J. Wellhausen, 1953-1960 (Box 12, Folder 141)
    - Corn Reports, 1943-1962 (Box 12, Folder 142)
    - Corn Reports, 1943-1962 (Box 12, Folder 143)
    - Corn Reports - Chromosomes - 1961 Corn Stunt Virus in Central America and Colombia - 1958 Corn Yield Tests - 1955-1956, 1955-1961 (Box 12, Folder 144)
    - Cornell University - 1958-1961 Corns, J.B. - 1958-1960 (Box 12, Folder 145)
    - Costa Rica - Central American Corn Improvement Project, 1956, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 146)
    - Costa Rica - Central American Corn Improvement Project, 1956, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 147)
    - Costa Rica - Central American Corn Improvement Project, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 148)
    - Costa Rica - Ensayos, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 149)
    - Costa Rica - General Correspondence, 1953-1955, 1958-1962 (Box 13, Folder 150)
    - Costa Rica - General Correspondence, 1953-1955, 1958-1962 (Box 13, Folder 151)
    - Costa Rica - General Correspondence, 1953-1955, 1958-1962 (Box 13, Folder 152)
    - Costa Rica - Instituto Interamericano de Ciencias Agricolas, 1945-1962 (Box 13, Folder 153)
    - Costa Rica - Instituto Interamericano de Ciencias Agricolas, 1945-1962 (Box 13, Folder 154)
    - Costa Rica - Instituto Interamericano de Ciencias Agricolas, 1945-1962 (Box 13, Folder 155)
    - Costa Rica - Reports, 1953, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 156)
    - Costa Rica - Smith, Donald L., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 157)
    - Covarrubias, Ramon - 1959 Cogwill, Ursula M. - 1960, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 158)
    - Crop Quality Control Council (Minnesota) - 1961-1962 Crop Science Society of America - 1961-1962 (Box 14, Folder 159)
    - Cuba General Correspondence - 1954-1961 Kevorkian, Arthur G. - 1946-1949, 1946-1961 (Box 14, Folder 160)
    - Customs - 1962 Czechoslovakia - 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 161)
    - Daza, Pablo E. - 1959-1960 DeKalb Agricultural Association, Inc. - 1961 De Lara Tours S.A. Mexico - 1961 Del Valle, C.G. (Florida) - 1960, 1959-1961 (Box 14, Folder 162)
    - Denys, Gustavo (El Salvador) - 1958 Department of Transportation (Mexico) - 1943-1956 (Box 14, Folder 163)
    - Derriengue, 1942-1945 (Box 14, Folder 164)
    - Development of Tropical Center (Chipas & Tabasco) - 1962 Diagnostic Laboratory (Chapingo) - 1958, 1958-1962 (Box 14, Folder 165)
    - Direccion de Conservacion del Suelo y el Agua (SAG) - 1946-1950 Direccion de Economia Rural (SAG) - 1955-1956 Direccion General de Aduanas - 1961-1962, 1946-1962 (Box 14, Folder 166)
    - Direccion General de Agricultura - Agricultural Extension Service - Agents, 1948-1949 (Box 14, Folder 167)
    - Direccion General de Agricultura - Agricultural Extension Service - General Correspondence, 1953-1961 (Box 15, Folder 168)
    - Direccion General de Agricultura - Agricultural Extension Service - General Correspondence, 1953-1961 (Box 15, Folder 169)
    - Direccion General de Agricultura - General Correspondence, 1946-1962 (Box 15, Folder 170)
    - Direccion General de Agricultura - General Correspondence, 1946-1962 (Box 15, Folder 171)
    - Direccion General de Agricultura - Plantings, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 172)
    - Direccion General de Agricultura - Wheat Department, 1957-1960 (Box 15, Folder 173)
    - Direccion General de Agricultura - Wheat Increase Program, 1954-1958 (Box 15, Folder 174)
    - Dominguez, Ricardo (Kellogg Foundation Fellow - El Salvador) - 1947-1949 Dominican Republic - 1959-1962, 1947-1962 (Box 15, Folder 175)
    - Durango, State of, 1955-1960 (Box 15, Folder 176)
    - Ecuador, 1959-1962 (Box 16, Folder 177)
    - Egypt - 1961-1962 Ellis, D.E. (North Carolina State University) - 1962 (Box 16, Folder 178)
    - El Salvador - Central American Corn Improvement Program, 1956, 1958-1961 (Box 16, Folder 179)
    - El Salvador - Central American Corn Improvement Program, 1956, 1958-1961 (Box 16, Folder 180)
    - El Salvador - General Correspondence, 1954-1963 (Box 16, Folder 181)
    - El Salvador - General Correspondence, 1954-1963 (Box 16, Folder 182)
    - El Salvador - General Correspondence, 1954-1963 (Box 16, Folder 183)
    - Embassies - 1959-1961 Enciso, Teodoro - 1962 England - 1959-1962 (Box 16, Folder 184)
    - Entomological Society of America, 1960-1962 (Box 16, Folder 185)
    - Entomology Reports, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 186)
    - Equipment - Farm and General Machinery, 1954-1956 (Box 16, Folder 187)
    - Equipment - Farm and General Machinery, 1959-1961 (Box 17, Folder 188)
    - Equipment - Farm and General Machinery, 1959-1961 (Box 17, Folder 189)
    - Equipment - Farm and General Machinery, 1959-1961 (Box 17, Folder 190)
    - Equipment - Supply Companies, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 191)
    - Escuela Agropecuaria de Sonora (Hermosillo), 1951-1954 (Box 17, Folder 192)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura (Chapingo) - Colegio de Post Graduatos - Advanced Genetics Course and Basic Food Course, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 193)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura (Chapingo) - Colegio de Post Graduatos Doctoral Process - 1958-1963 Financial Reports - 1959-1961 (Box 17, Folder 194)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura (Chapingo) - Colegio de Post Graduatos - General Corresponsdence, 1957-1960 (Box 17, Folder 195)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura (Chapingo) - Colegio de Post Graduatos - General Corresponsdence, 1957-1960 (Box 17, Folder 196)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura (Chapingo) - Colegio de Post Graduatos - General Corresponsdence, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 197)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura (Chapingo) - Colegio de Post Graduatos - General Corresponsdence, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 198)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura (Chapingo) - Colegio de Post Graduatos - General Corresponsdence, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 199)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura (Chapingo) - Colegio de Post Graduatos - Interamerican Research and Training Center, 1959-1962 (Box 18, Folder 200)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura (Chapingo) - Colegio de Post Graduatos - Programas de Ensenanza, 1959-1961 (Box 18, Folder 201)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura - Colegio de Post Graduatos - Projects, 1959-1961 (Box 18, Folder 202)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura - Colegio de Post Graduatos - Reports (Financial), 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 203)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura - Colegio de Post Graduatos - Wellhausen, E.J., 1959 (Box 18, Folder 204)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura Department of Parasitology - 1962 Equipment - 1955, 1955-1962 (Box 18, Folder 205)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura - General Correspondence, 1949-1958 (Box 18, Folder 206)
    - Escuela Nacional de Agricultura - General Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 19, Folder 207)
    - Escuela Normal Rural de Roque - (n.d.) Escuela Particular de Agricultura (Ciudad Juarez) - 1952-1957, 1961, 1952-1961 (Box 19, Folder 208)
    - Escuela Superior de Agricultura "Antonio Narro" - (Saltillo, Coahuila), 1952-1961 (Box 19, Folder 209)
    - Escuela Superior de Agricultura "Antonio Narro" - (Saltillo, Coahuila), 1952-1961 (Box 19, Folder 210)
    - Europe - 1961 Everett, Herbert L. (Cornell University) - 1960-1962 Experiment in International Living - 1959-1962 (Box 19, Folder 211)
    - FAO (Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations) - General Correspondence, 1953-1962 (Box 19, Folder 212)
    - FAO (Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations) - General Correspondence, 1953-1962 (Box 19, Folder 213)
    - FAO (Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations) - General Correspondence, 1953-1962 (Box 19, Folder 214)
    - FAO - Maize Meeting (Rome-Eucarpia Feburary 1960), 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 215)
    - Farmers Associations and Credit Unions, 1946-1956 (Box 20, Folder 216)
    - Fellowships (General) - 1960-1966 Fertilaid - 1954-1955 Fertilizers - 1955-1956, 1954-1966 (Box 20, Folder 217)
    - Fiji - 1962 First National Bank of New York - 1959-1961, 1959-1962 (Box 20, Folder 218)
    - Fish Pond Project - Fish Pond Sites, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 219)
    - Fish Pond Project - Fish Species, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 220)
    - Fish Pond Project - Jackson, Herbert W., 1949-1951 (Box 20, Folder 221)
    - Fletcher, Donald G. (Rust Prevention Association) - 1959-1960 Florida - 1959-1962 (Box 20, Folder 222)
    - Forage Grasses and Legumes, 1953-1960 (Box 20, Folder 223)
    - Ford Foundation - Fellows, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 224)
    - Ford Foundation - General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 225)
    - France - 1959-1962 Freeman, Wayne H. - 1961 Frolick, E.F. - 1959-1960, 1959-1961 (Box 20, Folder 226)
    - Galarraga, Jose Rafael (Point IV Fellow-Ecuador), 1953-1958 (Box 20, Folder 227)
    - General Correspondence (A-Z), 1949-1958 (Box 20, Folder 228)
    - General Correspondence - Africa and Asia, 1959-1962 (Box 20, Folder 229)
    - General Correspondence - Caribbean, 1959-1961 (Box 21, Folder 230)
    - General Correspondence - Central America, 1947-1960 (Box 21, Folder 231)
    - General Correspondence - Europe, 1959-1961 (Box 21, Folder 232)
    - General Correspondence - Mexico, 1960-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 233)
    - General Correspondence - Mexico, 1960-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 234)
    - General Correspondence - Mexico - Government Agencies, 1958-1962 (Box 21, Folder 235)
    - General Correspondence - Mexico - RF Staff, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 236)
    - General Correspondence - Mexico - Unofficial, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 237)
    - General Correspondence - North America (A-M), 1959-1962 (Box 21, Folder 238)
    - General Correspondence - North America (N-Z), 1959-1962 (Box 22, Folder 239)
    - General Correspondence - Smith, Donald L., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 240)
    - General Correspondence - South America, 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 241)
    - General Correspondence - Wellhausen, Edwin J., 1958-1962 (Box 22, Folder 242)
    - Geneticists Meeting I - (Sept. 26-Oct. 8, 1949 -- Mexico) - General Files (Box 22, Folder 243)
    - Geneticists Meeting II - (March 31-April 12, 1952 -- Brazil) - Delegates Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 244)
    - Geneticists Meeting II - (March 31-April 12, 1952 -- Brazil) - Delegates Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 245)
    - Geneticists Meeting II - General Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 246)
    - Geneticists Meeting II - Invitation List, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 247)
    - Geneticists Meeting II - Program, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 248)
    - Geneticists Meeting II - Telegrams, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 249)
    - Geneticists Meeting II - Titles Received, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 250)
    - Geneticists Meeting II - Travel, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 251)
    - Geneticists Meeting III (June 20-July 1, 1955 -- Colombia) - Correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 23, Folder 252)
    - Geneticists Meeting III - Program, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 253)
    - Genetics (W.M. Myers) - (n.d) Genetics Society of America - 1959-1962 (Box 23, Folder 254)
    - Georgia - 1962 Germ Plasm Conference - 1959 Germany - 1960-1962, 1959-1962 (Box 23, Folder 255)
    - Ghana - 1962 Gibler, John W. (Diary) - 1962 Gillham, Fred E.M. - 1962 Goppinger, Walter W. - 1962 (Box 23, Folder 256)
    - Gomez, Marte R. - (Secretario de Agricultura y Fomento-Mexico), 1944-1947 (Box 23, Folder 257)
    - Gonzalez Gallardo, Alfonso - (Sub-Secretario de Agricultura y Fomento-Mexico), 1943-1950 (Box 23, Folder 258)
    - Gonzalez Gallardo, Alfonso - (Sub-Secretario de Agricultura y Fomento-Mexico), 1943-1950 (Box 23, Folder 259)
    - Governmental Correspondence (Mexico), 1943-1950 (Box 23, Folder 260)
    - Great Britain - 1962 Green, V.E. (University of Florida) - 1962 Gregory, Walton C. (North Carolina State U.) - 1962 Grobman, Alexander (Harvard University) - 1960, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 261)
    - Guanajauto, State of, 1958-1961 (Box 23, Folder 262)
    - Guatemala - Arevalo, Boris, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 263)
    - Guatemala - Ensayo Observaciones de Colecciones, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 264)
    - Guatemala - Ensayo Observaciones de Colecciones, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 265)
    - Guatemala - Ensayo Uniformes de Rendimiento, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 266)
    - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 24, Folder 267)
    - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 24, Folder 268)
    - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 24, Folder 269)
    - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 24, Folder 270)
    - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 24, Folder 271)
    - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 272)
    - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 273)
    - Guatemala - Instituto Agropeacuario Nacional, 1947-1956 (Box 25, Folder 274)
    - Guatemala - Libros de Campo, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 275)
    - Guatemala - Reports, 1956-1962 (Box 25, Folder 276)
    - Guerrero, State of - 1952-1961 Guevara, Jose (I.N.I.A.) - 1962 Guinea - 1962 Gutierrez, Mario - 1961, 1952-1962 (Box 25, Folder 277)
    - Haag, Herman M - 1962 Haiti - 1959-1962 Hanson, Warren D. - 1961-1962 Hampstead, Dale - 1961 (Box 25, Folder 278)
    - Harrar, J.G. (George) - Correspondence, 1946-1956 (Box 25, Folder 279)
    - Harrar, J.G. (George) Diaries - 1943-1952 Five Year Report - 1943-1948 (Box 25, Folder 280)
    - Hartwig, Norman - 1961 Harvey, Paul H. - 1958-1961 Hatheway, William H. - 1959-1962 (Box 25, Folder 281)
    - Hawaii - 1962 Hayes, Guy S. - 1952-1956 Herbicides - 1958-1960, 1952-1962 (Box 25, Folder 282)
    - Hernandez, Efraim, 1953-1957 (Box 25, Folder 283)
    - Hidalgo, State of - 1950-1961 Hoffmann-Pinther and Bosworth S.A. - 1953-1956 Holland - 1960-1962, 1950-1962 (Box 26, Folder 284)
    - Honduras - Ensayo de Uniforme de Rendimiento, 1956, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 285)
    - Honduras - Escuela Agricola Panamericana, 1943-1956 (Box 26, Folder 286)
    - Honduras - General Correspondence, 1954-1959 (Box 26, Folder 287)
    - Honduras - General Correspondence, 1954-1959 (Box 26, Folder 288)
    - Honduras - General Correspondence, 1954-1959 (Box 26, Folder 289)
    - Honduras - General Correspondence, 1954-1959 (Box 26, Folder 290)
    - Honduras - General Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 26, Folder 291)
    - Honduras - General Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 26, Folder 292)
    - Horticulture Correspondence - 1958-1959 Reports - 1956-1960 (Box 26, Folder 293)
    - Hu, Wilma Wie-Lin - 1966 Hungary - 1962 Huss, Donald - 1962, 1962-1966 (Box 26, Folder 294)
    - Idaho - 1962 Illinois - 1959-1962 (Box 27, Folder 295)
    - Immigration Matters, 1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 296)
    - India - 1952 Indian Agricultural Program - 1958-1962 (Box 27, Folder 297)
    - Indiana University - 1959 Indonesia - 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 298)
    - Instituto de Investigaciones Agricolo (SAG), 1947-1958 (Box 27, Folder 299)
    - Instituto de Nutricion de Centro America y Panama, 1949-1957 (Box 27, Folder 300)
    - Instituto Mexicano Norteamericano de Relaciones Culturales, 1959-1961 (Box 27, Folder 301)
    - Instituto Mexicano Norteamericano de Relaciones Culturales, 1959-1961 (Box 27, Folder 302)
    - Instituto Nacional de Investigaciones Agricolas (INIA) Animal Nutrition - 1961-1962 Budgets - 1962 Construction Project INIA Headquarters - 1962 (Box 27, Folder 303)
    - INIA Department of Agricultural Economy - 1961-1962 Department of Beans and Soybeans - 1961-1962 Department of Cereals - 1961-1962 Department of Entomology - 1961 (Box 27, Folder 304)
    - INIA Department of Forages - 1961-1962 Department of Herbicides - 1961 Department of Horticulture - 1961-1962 Department of Oil Plants - 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 305)
    - INIA Department of Plant Pathology - 1961-1962 Department of Technical Promotion - 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 306)
    - INIA - Department of Zootechnia, 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 307)
    - INIA Director General - 1961-1962 General Correspondence - 1961-1962 Maize and Sorghum Section - 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 308)
    - INIA - Personnel - Curriculum Vitae, 1960-1962 (Box 28, Folder 309)
    - INIA - Personnel - General, 1960-1962 (Box 28, Folder 310)
    - INIA - Personnel - Projected Needs for Trained Personnel, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 311)
    - INIA Presidential Decree - 1960 Project Committee - 1962 Publications Committee - 1962, 1960-1962 (Box 28, Folder 312)
    - INIA - Reorganization of Research Activities, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 313)
    - INIA - Reorganization of Research Activities, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 314)
    - INIA - Rules and Procedures, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 315)
    - INIA - Seed Laboratory, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 316)
    - INIA Subdirector Jose Guevara Calderon - 1961-1962 Subdirector N. Sanchez Duron - 1961-1962 Subdirector Jose Luis Spota - 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 317)
    - INIA - Workshops, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 318)
    - Instituto Nacional de Investigacion Pecuaria, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 319)
    - Instituto Nacional de Nutriologia, 1948-1954 (Box 28, Folder 320)
    - Instituto Nacional de Nutriologia - Statistics, 1948-1951 (Box 29, Folder 321)
    - Instituto para el Mejoramiento de la Produccion de Azucar - 1958-1960 Instituto Politechnio Nacional - 1947 Instituto Technologico Azucarera Veracruzano - 1960, 1947-1960 (Box 29, Folder 322)
    - Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores Monterrey - Campo Apodaca, 1954-1956 (Box 29, Folder 323)
    - Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores Monterrey - General Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 29, Folder 324)
    - Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores Monterrey - General Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 29, Folder 325)
    - Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores Monterrey - General Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 29, Folder 326)
    - Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores Monterrey - Leonel Robles (Correspondence), 1948-1959 (Box 29, Folder 327)
    - Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores Monterrey - Leonel Robles (Correspondence), 1948-1959 (Box 29, Folder 328)
    - Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores Monterrey - School of Agronomy, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 329)
    - Insurance, 1959-1961 (Box 30, Folder 330)
    - Inter-American Congress of Farmers and Agronomists, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 331)
    - Inter-American Corn Crop Improvement Program, 1959-1962 (Box 30, Folder 332)
    - Inter-American Food Crop Improvement Program, 1959-1962 (Box 30, Folder 333)
    - Inter-American Maize Improvement Program, 1959-1961 (Box 30, Folder 334)
    - Inter-American Research Symposium (Role of Communications in Agricultural Development), October 5-13, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 335)
    - Inter-American Society for Plant and Soil Scientists - 4th Annual Meeting (Chile), November 25-December 1, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 336)
    - Inter-American Society for Plant and Soil Scientists - 5th Annual Meeting (Argentina), November 5-18, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 337)
    - Inter-American Wheat Improvement Program, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 338)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - 1961 International Corn Breeding Program - 1961 International Cultural Center, A.C. - 1960-1961 (Box 30, Folder 339)
    - International Rice Research Institute - 1963-1965 International Wheat Improvement Program - 1959-1960, 1959-1965 (Box 30, Folder 340)
    - International Wheat Rust Conference, March 18-24, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 341)
    - Iowa - 1958-1962 Iowa State College/University - 1953-1954, 1959-1961, 1953-1962 (Box 31, Folder 342)
    - Iraq - 1962 Israel - 1962 Italy - 1959-1962 (Box 31, Folder 343)
    - Jalisco, State of, 1953-1962 (Box 31, Folder 344)
    - Jamaica - 1957-1962 Japan - 1962 (Box 31, Folder 345)
    - Jenkins, Merle T. - 1961 Jimenez, Jose - 1959 Jimenez, Mario Gutierrez - 1961-1962, 1959-1962 (Box 31, Folder 346)
    - Johnson, E.C. - 1961-1962 Johnston, John - 1962 Jordan - 1962 (Box 31, Folder 347)
    - Kansas - 1958-1959 Kellogg Foundation Fellows-General - 1947-1949 Kellogg Foundation Fellows-Romero Lainez, Roberto - 1947-1949, 1962, 1947-1962 (Box 31, Folder 348)
    - Kentucky - 1962 Kenya - 1959-1962 (Box 31, Folder 349)
    - Latin-American Soils Scientists Meeting - October 19-24, 1953 Leng, Earl R. - 1961 Liberia - 1961, 1953-1961 (Box 31, Folder 350)
    - Livestock Improvement Project - 1953 Longley, Albert E. - 1959-1962 (Box 31, Folder 351)
    - Lonnquist, John H. - 1959-1962 Louisiana - 1962 Louisiana State University Library - 1960 (Box 31, Folder 352)
    - McClintock, Barbara - 1959-1962 McKelvey, John J. - 1945-1951, 1945-1962 (Box 32, Folder 353)
    - McNeish, Richard S. - 1960-1962 Madagascar - 1960-1962 (Box 32, Folder 354)
    - Maize Committee (Minutes) - 1959 Maize Reports - 1959 Mazie Seed Shipments - 1962, 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 355)
    - Malca, Isaac - 1962 Mali, Republic of - 1962 Mangelsdorf, Paul C. - 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 356)
    - MAP (Mexican Agricultural Program) - Abstracts, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 357)
    - MAP - Activity Reports, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 358)
    - MAP - Advisory Committee and Trustee Reports, 1945-1951 (Box 32, Folder 359)
    - MAP - Advisory Committee and Trustee Reports, 1945-1951 (Box 32, Folder 360)
    - MAP - Advisory Committee and Trustee Reports, 1945-1951 (Box 32, Folder 361)
    - MAP - Advisory Committee and Trustee Reports - Correspondence, 1949-1951 (Box 32, Folder 362)
    - MAP - Applicants-Staff Positions, 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 363)
    - MAP - Budget, 1957, 1962, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 364)
    - MAP - Diaries, 1944-1962 (Box 33, Folder 365)
    - MAP - Diaries and Memoranda, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 366)
    - MAP Entertainment - 1960-1962 Federal Subsidy - 1955-1958, 1955-1960 (Box 33, Folder 367)
    - MAP - Fellows-Non RF, 1953-1958 (Box 33, Folder 368)
    - MAP - Film Project - "Mexican Agricultural Program", 1950 (Box 33, Folder 369)
    - MAP - Form Letters, 1953-1962 (Box 33, Folder 370)
    - MAP - Friends and Collaborators, 1960-1962 (Box 33, Folder 371)
    - MAP Grants-Scholarships - 1943-1963 Grants-Travel - 1963-1966, 1943-1966 (Box 33, Folder 372)
    - MAP - Invitations, 1961-1962 (Box 33, Folder 373)
    - MAP - Itineraries, 1959-1962 (Box 33, Folder 374)
    - MAP Library - 1959-1962 Living Accomodations - 1959-1964 (Box 33, Folder 375)
    - MAP - Memoranda, 1946, 1948, 1950, 1952, 1955, 1957-1962 (Box 34, Folder 376)
    - MAP - Memoranda, 1946, 1948, 1950, 1952, 1955, 1957-1962 (Box 34, Folder 377)
    - MAP - Memoranda, 1946, 1948, 1950, 1952, 1955, 1957-1962 (Box 34, Folder 378)
    - MAP - Memoranda, 1946, 1948, 1950, 1952, 1955, 1957-1962 (Box 34, Folder 379)
    - MAP - Orders-Supplies, Equipment, Seeds, 1959-1962 (Box 34, Folder 380)
    - MAP - Reports, 1950-1962 (Box 34, Folder 381)
    - MAP - Reports, 1950-1962 (Box 34, Folder 382)
    - MAP - Six Year Review (J.G. Harrar), 1943-1949 (Box 34, Folder 383)
    - MAP - Staff - Directory and Organization, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 384)
    - MAP - Staff - Long Distance Telephone Calls, 1960-1962 (Box 34, Folder 385)
    - MAP - Staff - Meetings, 1950-1958 (Box 34, Folder 386)
    - MAP - Staff - Personnel, 1960-1962 (Box 35, Folder 387)
    - MAP - Visitors, 1960-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 388)
    - MAP - Visitors, 1960-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 389)
    - MAP - Visitors, 1960-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 390)
    - MAP - Workshops, 1956-1957 (Box 35, Folder 391)